Guide to the Stanford University, School of Humanities and Sciences, Innovative Academic Courses, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1992-086
  - SWOP 150 Autistic/ Schizo/ Emotionally Disturbed Children Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - SWOP 151 Asian American Process Through Radio Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - SWOP 152: Stonecloud Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - SWOP 154 Women's Health Counseling, Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - SWOP 155 Bicycles Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - SWOP 156: Enlightened Peasantry Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - SWOP 161 Project Synergy Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - SWOP 168C Behavior Mod./ Classroom Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - SWOP 169C Change and the Church Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - SWOP 173B Alternative Schools Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - SWOP 181B Students/ Univ. Gov. Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - SWOP 182C New Towns Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - SWOP 189 Social Values in Day Care Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - SWOP 186B Movements and Minorites Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - SWOP 192: Emotionally Disabled/Comm. Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - SWOP 193B Latin America/ US Press Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - SWOP 194 Political Organizing, Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - SWOP 195 Bicultural Praxis Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - SWOP 101 Social Behavor Change Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - SWOP 102 Sign Language and Problems of the Deaf, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - SWOP 103 California Agricultural Labor, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - SWOP 104 Labor Unions in the Ô70's Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - SWOP 105 The Dating Game: Dating and Courtship Patterns at Stanford, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - SWOP 106 Immigration Laws and Problems, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - SWOP 107 Age Discrimination in America, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - SWOP 109 A&B Peer Counseling Techniques: the bridge, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - SWOP 120 Autistic and Schizophrenic Children, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - SWOP 121 Being Handicapped, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - SWOP 123 Pretrial detention and release, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - SWOP 161B Project Synergy Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - SWOP 130 Government Regulation of the Economy California Agriculture, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - SWOP 131 Black Perspectives in Media, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - SWOP 132 Computers and Social Responsibility, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - SWOP 133 Prisons, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - SWOP 134 Women's Studies, CROW Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - SWOP 135 Welfare, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - SWOP 142 Child Care: Ways of Growing, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - SWOP 161 A&B Project Synergy, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - SWOP 168B Behavior Mod. Classroom, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - SWOP 174Aand B Workshop on Women, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - SWOP 186 Minorities in the Media, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - SWOP 192 Disturbed Persons in the Community, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - SWOP 197B Alternatives in Family Relations and Foster Care: Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - SWOP 198B Evangelical Politics, Not Approved, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - SWOP 101 Social Behavior Change, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - SWOP 120B Sign Language/ Problems of the Deaf, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - SWOP 107 Age Discrimination, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - SWOP 109 Peer Counseling, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - SWOP 120C Autisitc/Schizophrenic Children, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - SWOP 121B Being Handicapped, CAR Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - SWOP 123B Pretial Release, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - SWOP 124 Racism and Education, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - SWOP 130B California Agriculture, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - SWOP 131 Plack Perspectives/Media Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - SWOP 132B Computers Social responsibility, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - SWOP 136 Social Sciences at Stanford, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - SWOP 142 Child Care Ways of Growing, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - SWOP 143 Medicine and Alternatives, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - SWOP 144 Global Simulation Models, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - SWOP 145 Unsanctioned City, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - SWOP 154 Contraceptive Counseling, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - SWOP 161 Project Synergy, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - SWOP 168C Behavior Modification, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - SWOP 174 Workshop on Women, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - SWOP 175 Workshop on Men, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - SWOP 176 Affirmative Action, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - SWOP 185 the political Economy of the Envionment, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - SWOP 192 Emotionally Disturbed Persons, Spring 1975 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - SWOP 111 Teatro: Politics or Art? Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - SWOP 112 Studying Child Dev. Block Building, Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - SWOP 113 Illegal Aliens, Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - SWOP 120 Volunteer Work With Severly Disturbed Children, Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - SWOP 121 Meaning of Being Handicapped, Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - SWOP 142 Child Care Ways of Growing, Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - SWOP 146 Strategies of the Information revolution, Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - SWOP 168 Working in Behav. Mod. Clsrm. Yng. Hndicapped Children, Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - SWOP 177 Women's Liberation and Public Policy, Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - SWOP 178 Workshop on Sex Roles, Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - SWOP 180 Nuclear Power: who decides? Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - SWOP 181 Land Trusts and Com. housng, Co-Ops, Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - SWOP 192 Helping the Emotionally disabled, Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - SWOP 197 Crisis in Nuclear Fam./ Juvenile Justice, Fall 1975 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - SWOP 111B Performing Teatro del Barrio, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - SWOP 113B Illegal Aliens, in the Work Force, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - SWOP 115 Alternatives on Education Where Do We fit In? Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - SWOP 116 Huelga School Community Education Project, Delano, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - SWOP 121B Experience Based Study on the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - SWOP 135 Welfare, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - SWOP 142 Child Care: ways of Growing Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - SWOP 154 Contraceptive Counseling, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - SWOP 156 The Voluntary Sector; Past, Present and Future, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - SWOP 168B Working in a Behavior Mod. Classroom, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - SWOP 177B Sex Discrimination on Employment, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - SWOP 178 Workshop on Sex Roles, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - SWOP 180B Nuclear Power, Who Will Decide? Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - SWOP 181B How To Find a Landlord You Can Live With: Land Trusts, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - SWOP 182: Prisoners and the Legal Systems, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - SWOP 192B Helping the Emotionally Disabled, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - SWOP 197B Developing New Models for Family relations and Juv. Justice, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - SWOP 111 Teatro del Barrio- Politics or Art? Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - SWOP 116B Huelga School Communication Project, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - SWOP 120C Vol. Work w/Severely Dist. Children, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - SWOP 121 Experience Based Study on the Meaning of being Handicapped, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - SWOP 142A and B, Child Care, Ways of Growing, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - 154 Contraceptive Counseling, Winter 1976 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - SWOP 178, Workshop on Sexism, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - SWOP 183 Taking Apart the Wat Machine Conversting Mid-Pen. defence Indus. Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - SWOP 184 Pinto, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - SWOP 115 Alternatives in Education, Fall 1976 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - SWOP 185 The Political Economy of the Environment, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - SWOP 186 Lifestyles in a Global Village, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - SWOP 187 Bilingual Bicultural Eduction, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - SWOP 188 Consumer Issues: Legal and Political, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - SWOP 189 Values in Transistion in a Pluristic Society, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - SWOP 190 Role of Historic Preservation and Conservation in Modern Society, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - SWOP 192 Helping the Emotionally Disabled, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - SWOP 193 Sexism in Education, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - SWOP 194 Political Organizing Techniques, Spring 1976 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - SWOP 120 Volunteer Work With Severly Disturbed Children,Fall 1976 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - SWOP 121B Experience Based Study on the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Fall 1976 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - SWOP 142 Day Care: Theory and Practice Fall 1976 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - SWOP 170 The Organizer: Community Organizing and Effecting Social Change, Dall 1976 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - SWOP 171 History of the American Labor Mvt. Fall 1976 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - SWOP 173 Carter vs. Ford: the Race to the White House, Fall 1976 (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - SWOP 174 Therapy: A Critical Introduction, Fall 1976 (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - SWOP 133, Appropriate Technology for Developing and Developed Countires, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - SWOP 177 Organizing for Equality: the Women's Mvt. Today, Fall 1976 (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - SWOP 178 Workshop on Sexism, Fall 1976 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - SWOP 197 Juvenile Justice: An Exploration and Field Placement, Fall 1976 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - SWOP 100 Methods and Approaches of Community Research, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - SWOP 115B Alternatives in Education, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - SWOP 120B Volunteer Work With Severly Disturbed Children Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - SWOP 121B Experience Based Study on the Meaning of being Handipcapped, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 89)
  - SWOP 130 The Evolution of Holistic Health, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - SWOP 131 Alcoholism, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 91)
  - SWOP 132 Planning for the Earthquake winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 92)
  - SWOP 134 Co-ops In the Bay Area, An Alternative, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - SWOP 136 Consumer Awareness in Automobils, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - SWOP 137: The Left and American Labor, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - SWOP 138 Changing Work in Capitalist America, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 96)
  - SWOP 139 the American Left Since Vietnam, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - SWOP 140 American Conservative Thought and Politics Since WWII, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 98)
  - SWOP 142 Group Care: An Alternative, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 99)
  - SWOP 143 The Social and Political Issues of Day care, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 100)
  - SWOP 145 Female Sexuality: reality and Fiction, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 101)
  - SWOP 147 Politics of Survival Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 102)
  - SWOP 172B A Recycling Plan for Stanford, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - SWOP 177B The Women's Movement Today, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - SWOP 178 Workshop on Sexism, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - SWOP 185 Political Economy of the Enviornment, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 106)
  - SWOP 187 Bilingual Bicultural Education, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 107)
  - SWOP 190 Preserving and Revitalizing Historic Areas, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 108)
  - SWOP 141 The Role of Students in Univer. Governance, Winter 1977 (Box 14, Folder 109)
  - SWOP 100B Methods of Change, Social research and Action, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - SWOP 120B Volunteer Work With Severly disturbed Children, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - SWOP 121B Experience Based Study on the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - SWOP 130B Evolution of Holistic Health, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - SWOP 131B Research in Teenage Drinking, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - SWOP 138B New Ways to Work, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - SWOP 142: Cooperative Child Care Centers Political and Practical Problems, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - SWOP 147 Nuclear ProliferationL Prospects for Control, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - SWOP 148: International Hunger: Institutional and Indiv. Responses, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - SWOP 149 Discrim. for Housing, Policy and Practice, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - SWOP 150, University Food Service, A Study of Priorities, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - SWOP 151 Student Influence in Education Western Civ. and Tenure, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - SWOP 153 Biol. and Social Aspects of Genetic Engineering, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - SWOP 154: Strateies for Change at Stanford, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - SWOP 156, Tenant-Landlord Relations: A Midpeninsual Perspective, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - SWOP 173: Energy and Conservation as an Energy Resource Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - SWOP 179 Workshop on Sexism II: Strategies within Feminism, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - SWOP 187B Bilingual and Bicultural Education, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - SWOP 190B Preserving and Revitalizing Historic Areas Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - SWOP 193: The Univ. as an Institutional Investor, Ethics and Profits, Spring 1977 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - SWOP 120: Volunteer Work With Severly Disturbed Children, Fall 1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - SWOP 121: Experience Based Study on the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Fall 1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - SWOP 142: Experiences in Child Care, Fall 1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - SWOP 160: Gaming /Simulation and Public Planning Process, Fall 1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - SWOP 161 Justice and Liberation, Fall 1977 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - SWOP 162 The Movement for Gay Liberation, Fall 1977 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - SWOP 163, Self Defense for Women, Fall 1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - SWOP 173B Energy Conservation as An Energy Resource, Fall 1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - SWOP 177 A Closer Look at Feminism, Fall 1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - SWOP 178 Politics and the White Goddess, Women's Poetry, Fall 1977 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - SWOP 110 Theater and Politics, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - SWOP 120 Volunteer Work With Serverly Disturbed Children, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - SWOP 121B Experience-Based Study of the Meaning of Being Handicapped. Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - SWOP 139: Human Rights: What Are They and Where Are They? Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - SWOP 142: Children and Childcare, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - SWOP 149: International Hunger and US AID, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - SWOP 150 Human Biology From A Leftist Feminist Perspective, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - SWOP 155: (Econ 198) California Housing Marked Land Booms and Bursting Bubbles, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - SWOP 157, The Changing Role of Science in Society: Who Shall Decide? Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - SWOP 161: Justice and Liberation Stuggles, A Theological Reflection, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - SWOP 163B Self-Defence for Women, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - SWOP 173C Energy Conservation as an Engery Resource, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - SWOP 175: Water and California, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - SWOP 117b What are We Fighting For? A Closer Look at Feminism, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - SWOP 180, Workshop on Sexism, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - SWOP 185: the Political Economy of the Environment, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - SWOP 187: The Practice and Politics of Bilingual And Bicultural Education, Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - SWOP 193 League of Califorina Cities as Social Planning Model, Urban Devel. Winter 1978 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - SWOP 104: Social Change and Personal Lifestyles, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - SWOP 106: Anarachism and Anarchirst: Organizing, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - SWOP 108 Nonviolent Resistance: Personal and Political Perspectives, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - SWOP 110B Theatre and Politics, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - 120B Volunteer Work With Serverly Disturbed Children, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - SWOP 121 Experience Based Study on the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - SWOP 127: Feminist Economics: Visions and Revisions, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - SWOP 133 Appropriate Technology, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - SWOP 135: ModernTechnology and the Invasion of Privacy, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - SWOP 139B Human Rights, What are They and Where are They? Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - SWOP 142 Children and Child Care, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - SWOP 149: International Hunger and US Aid, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - SWOP 163: Issues in Self Defence for Women, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - SWOP 165 On Being Male, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - SWOP 174 A Recycling Plan for Stanford, Fall 1977 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - SWOP 175: Conservation as an Energy Resource:The Solarizarion of Stanford, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - SWOP 182: Southeast Asia in the World Capitalist Economy, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - SWOP 186, Asian Amiericans and the Media Emergining Perspectives, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - SWOP 187B The Practice and Politics of Bilingual and Bicultural Education, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - SWOP 195: Institutional Policies and Their Impacts on Society, How to Decide? Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - SWOP 196: California Politics: campaign Tactics and Strategies, Spring 1978 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - SWOP 110 Contemporary Marxism: Theory and Practice, Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - SWOP 120 Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - SWOP 121 Experinace-Based Study of the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - SWOP 122: Children's Health Council: Exceptional Children, Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - SWOP 138: Communities Organizing for Health, Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - SWOP 142: Cooperative Child Care: Political and Social Issues, Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - SWOP 151: Bioethics and the Nuclear Age, Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - SWOP 155, Space Colonization, Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - SWOP 163: Issues in Self-Defence for Women, Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - SWOP 170: Solar Software, Instituational Changes, Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - SWOP 177 Feminism, What are We fighting For? Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - SWOP 178: Women's Poetry and Politics, Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - SWOP 110, Contemporary Marxism, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - SWOP 120A Working Effectively With Disturbed Children, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - SWOP 120B Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - SWOP 121: Experience Based Study on the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - SWOP 122B Exceptional Children Rights and Responsibilities, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - SWOP 123, Med. Psych. and Soc. Adjustment to Spinal Cord Injury, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - SWOP 149: International Hunger and US Aid, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - SWOP 155 Space Colonization, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - SWOP 162: Homosexuality: An Overview Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - SWOP 171 American Wilderness Policy Pol. of Preservation, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - SWOP 172: Waste Age: the effects of Consumption, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - SWOP 180: Workshop on Sexism, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - SWOP 181: Asian American Art, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - SWOP 184: Victim/Witness Assistance: Community Responsibility, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - SWOP 187: Prac. and Pol. of Bilingual Bicultural Education, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - SWOP 192: The Fine Art of getting Elected: A Local Experience, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - SWOP 195: Public Policy Issues in Education, Winter 1979 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - SWOP 112: Consumer Boycotts: Selected Cases,Cancelled, Spring 1979 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - SWOP 120A Working Effectively With Disturbed Children, Spring 1979 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - SWOP 120B Working Effectively With Disturbed Children, Spring 1979 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - SWOP 121: Exp-Based Study on the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Spring 1979 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - SWOP 122A CHC-A Multidisip. App. to Except. Children, Spring 1979 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - SWOP 124: Stanford University Medical Center: An Ideological Crisis, Spring 1979 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - SWOP 134 Native American Destiny: who Controlls it? Spring 1979 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - SWOP 140: Soviet Human Rights: An Analysis of Prespective, Spring 1979 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - SWOP 142: Copperative Child Care: Soc. and Polit. Issues, Spring 1979 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - SWOP 145: Action for Soviet Jews, Spring 1979 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - SWOP 146: Conflicts and Choices on US Foreign Policy, Spring 1979 (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - SWOP 147: the Development of Modern Terrorism, Spring 1979 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - SWOP 155: Space Colonization, Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - SWOP 162 B: Homosexuality: An Overview, Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - SWOP 171: American Wilderness: Politics of Preservation, Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - SWOP 175: Women in the Professions Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - SWOP 176: The Politics of Birth Control, Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - SWOP 179: Marxist-Feminism: Dissolving the Hyphen, Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - SWOP 182: Asian American Communities, Issues and Answers, Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - SWOP 183: Asian American Women; Significance of Expression, Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - SWOP 184 Justice, the Victim, and Witness of Crime, Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - SWOP 188: (Comm 155/255) Women in the Mass Media, Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - SWOP 192 B: Fine Art of Getting Elected: A Local Experience, Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - SWOP 196: Education for Critical Consciousness, Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - SWOP 197: Crisis in the High School, Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - SWOP 120A: Working Effectively With Disturbed Children, Autumn 1979 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - SWOP 121: Exp-Based Study of the Meaning of Being Handicapped, Autumn 1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - SWOP 122A- CHC: Teaching Learning Handicapped Children, Autumn 1979 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - SWOP 133, Appropriate Technology, Postponed, Autumn 1979 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - SWOP 144: Decision Making in International Affiars, Not Approved, Autumn 1979 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - SWOP 149, International Hunger and US Aid, Autumn 1979 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - SWOP 151 The Politics of Radiation, Autumn 1979 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - SWOP 169: Whales and Whaling, Politics and Action, Autumn 1979 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - SWOP 173: Domestic Violence: Myth and Reality, Autumn 1979 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - SWOP 174: Women and the Political Process: A Local Experience, Autumn 1979 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - SWOP 185: The Juvenile Justice System, Autumn 1979 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - SWOP 198: Ethical Issues in Business, Autumn 1979 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - SWOP 107: Political and Social Issues of Aging, Winter 1980 (Box 16, Folder 26)